{
  "html": {
    "title": "HTML",
    "arr": [
      {
        "level": "1",
        "question": "Вопрос 1",
        "answer": "Ответ 2",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      },
      {
        "level": "1",
        "question": "Вопрос 2",
        "answer": "Ответ 3",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      },
      {
        "level": "1",
        "question": "Вопрос 3",
        "answer": "Ответ 1",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      },
      {
        "level": "2",
        "question": "Вопрос 4",
        "answer": "Ответ 4",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      },
      {
        "level": "2",
        "question": "Вопрос 5",
        "answer": "Ответ 1",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      },
      {
        "level": "3",
        "question": "Вопрос 6",
        "answer": "Ответ 2",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "css": {
    "title": "CSS",
    "arr": [
      {
        "level": "1",
        "question": "Вопрос 1",
        "answer": "Ответ 2",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      },
      {
        "level": "1",
        "question": "Вопрос 2",
        "answer": "Ответ 3",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      },
      {
        "level": "1",
        "question": "Вопрос 3",
        "answer": "Ответ 1",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      },
      {
        "level": "2",
        "question": "Вопрос 4",
        "answer": "Ответ 4",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      },
      {
        "level": "2",
        "question": "Вопрос 5",
        "answer": "Ответ 1",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      },
      {
        "level": "3",
        "question": "Вопрос 6",
        "answer": "Ответ 2",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "javascript": {
    "title": "JavaScript",
    "arr": [
      {
        "level": "1",
        "question": "Вопрос 1",
        "answer": "Ответ 2",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      },
      {
        "level": "1",
        "question": "Вопрос 2",
        "answer": "Ответ 3",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      },
      {
        "level": "1",
        "question": "Вопрос 3",
        "answer": "Ответ 1",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      },
      {
        "level": "2",
        "question": "Вопрос 4",
        "answer": "Ответ 4",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      },
      {
        "level": "2",
        "question": "Вопрос 5",
        "answer": "Ответ 1",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      },
      {
        "level": "3",
        "question": "Вопрос 6",
        "answer": "Ответ 2",
        "answerArr": [
          "Ответ 1",
          "Ответ 2",
          "Ответ 3",
          "Ответ 4"
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
}
